Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Good Morning, Sir
Go to hell
Boss
"I control people's fate. They are at my mercy"
"They are delusive. I cannot totally
understand mankind"
"The conflicts amongst humans"
"Are vaster than the oceans"
"Between the good and the evil"
"it's hard to draw the line"
I was being hunted down again twice this month
I need a pay raise, even a little is good
What is it? We can't talk?
I...
go...
to watch...
sexy dance?
"Read this in a private place"
Listen carefully - this is
a very important mission
If you succeed, you...
can save the whole world
Understood
Dr Peterson, professor of
a university in Switzerland
had invented a seed that will
startle the universe and stir the ghosts
It's called the Seed of God
Bury it in sand
Sprinkle some water, and within a minute,
it will sprout and bear fruit
That sounds a bit dramatic
They are now taking this Seed of God
to Shenzhen to a company that
sponsored this project - Haotian Technology
They will give a demonstration of this
seed to the company's president - Louis Luo
Oh, you mean the famous Luo family that
has been stealing to help the poor
from generation to generation
Louis' father had washed his hands off
the theft business
Some said in his will,
he exhorted his five kids that
they should never steal to help the poor again
That's why his second son, Louis Luo,
started Haotian Technology
to do scientific researches
He is now a hugely rich man
I want you to get yourself into this company
This tablet will detonate in 10 seconds
You have 5 seconds left
Time's up!
Mom, I'm home
Amon, what happened to your Ninjutsu skill,
it's getting worse and worse
All these years of learning are a waste of time
You asked me to give you
a sneak attack from time to time
So you can upkeep your deftness
That's right, but there is not
a slightest improvement on your end
That's hardly any challenge to me?
Can't you feel a little breeze
coming from behind?
Funny I do feel a breeze now
that you mentioned it
Why?
Aren't we great buddies,
we have the same taste for underpants
How is that possible?
My size is obviously bigger than yours
Louis
You didn't get hurt, did you?
What do you think?
Let me rub it for you
Louis, I'm a big girl now,
you can't rub for me
You're right
I'm a big boy too, you can't rub for me either
Are you out of your mind?
I could have hurt Ka-yan.
How could you do that?
Louis
But I am the descendent
of the famous Luo family
I have to master my fighting skills too
I can't ruin our family name
traveling in the world
You think you can travel the world
with that pathetic kung-fu skills of yours
What shall I tell Mom
if anything happens to you?
What do you want to tell me?
- Mom
- Come,Baby
Mom
Why are you still up at this hour?
I have to make sure you drink the soup.
I know you won't otherwise
This soup is really nourishing
Yes, it's good for your lungs
Drink it while it's still hot
Dementia is really getting
to her head these days
Yesterday, she mistook me for her dog
Meatball
Come on, drink it while it's hot
It's good for you
Just drink it
It's for your own good
Son, it's really flavorful. Isn't it?
It can't get any fresher than this
You guys chat. I'm sleepy
Mom, you should go to bed
Mom, be careful
Oh, Meatball has been such a good boy today
He hasn't made a sound all day
That's right. He's always been good
Son, I was just going over some old stuff
And I came across this secret book
of martial arts that your father wrote
The Art of Breaking Free
I have learnt it before
Shall I teach you now?
Sure
"Teddyboy"
Mom, on second thoughts,
I guess I had better practise by myself later
Oh
You can't handle it on your own
I have to help you
HOW?
Like this
So now you figure it out yourself
And within 6 hours
You will get the hang of it
And you will be able to break free
Understand?
I understand, Mom
Good boy
Ka-yan, untie me! Quick!
Mom wants you to practise on your own.
You should work on it
I dare not do anything against her will
Amon
Amon, help!
Help me, Amon
I thought
You love this kind of stuff
I will cut your pay!
You traitor!
Don't turn the lights off!
I'm afraid of the dark!
Help!
Good morning, Mr Luo
Good morning, President Luo
Louis, looks like your company has
a lot of good-looking staff
Even the janitor is so handsome!
Today, there will be a professor
from Switzerland
coming to demonstrate a magical seed
Its value is phenomenal
Sol...
Mr Luo, Mr Stephen Stone
and Dr Peterson have arrived
- Mr Luo, it's been a while
- Yes, it's been a while
Thank you for working so hard on
this research, Dr Peterson
Finally, we meet in person
The Seed of God - just add water,
and it will grow into any
kind of crop in no time
If this really works out,
that means all the famine
in poor countries will be solved?
Because its outcome is so spectacular,
I have decided to give you
a demonstration in person today
This is just sand. How can it grow anything?
That is the marvel of it
Unbelievable
This is a miracle
Is it edible?
Definitely. Try it
It does taste and smell sweet, doesn't it?
In other words, we can even
grow apples in a desert
Just add water, and you can grow anything
This Seed of God will undoubtedly put
an end to famine
But on the other hand,
it will also drive a lot of
agricultural countries to brankruptcy
Stop
There is a meeting going on inside
You cannot enter
Attack
Don't make a move
This is the latest technology - sonic gun.
We are not her match
Take him with us
We're done. Come over now
What the hell is that?
You...
Professor
Come with us if you want to live
Let's go
Aren't you the handsome janitor
outside the toilet?
Hey, be polite
Louis Luo
lam...
I know who you are
Sir Sampan
Agent code 119
You are the agent that
caused the most trouble in the Interpol
Last year, for trying to catch a thief
that snatched a handbag
You wrecked 103 cars
plus a motorboat and an airplane
I see Interpol is on the case now
No wonder the press
hasn't mentioned anything about it
That's right
Because we don't want to arouse any panic
We hope to retrieve the Seed of God
in the shortest time possible
Shouldn't you be somewhere looking for it now?
Why are you in my house?
I want you to work with me
I'm just a normal civilian. How can I help you?
No...
Louis Luo
I know who you are
For the past 30+ generations,
the whole Luo family have been thieves
We were robinhoods
And we have quit long time ago
Honey
Who are you?
Mom...
Good girl...
Come here...
Who are you, young lady?
You just love joking around
Amnesia and other bullshit
You don't remember me?
You don't have to explain...
I'm just happy you're back
I made soup, I'll get you the soup
Mom...
The good soup should be served to...
Dad
That's right
You wait here
Okay
- Who is that?
- My mom
She has a little bit of Dementia
She always mixes up people and things
Okay, I am happy to play along with that
Mind if we talk in private?
We have nothing to talk about
The Interpol has a strong team of great agents
Why am I needed?
The story is...
That our computer system has been hacked
All the Interpol agents' IDs have been leaked
I need your help
I appreciate that thought
But I'm still not gonna help you
The Seed-of-God project was sponsored by you
And it was ultimately being
robbed in your company
You cannot evade accountability
I know who took the Seed of God
A Japanese Criminal Organization
called Crescent,
headed by a woman named Snow
But there is one thing you are not aware of
The professor was not abducted
He is an accomplice that
led them to rob the Seed of God
Then they will sell the seeds to
the biggest criminal syndicate
K-MAX
Just think about this
If the Seed of God falls into
the hands of K-MAX, what will happen?
There is no time for hesitation.
Let's have a contest
If you lose, you come with me
This is my phone
I put it here in this pocket
If you can get it within a minute, I lose
No...
I put the phone here
If you can get it within a minute,
I lose
Come on
Meatball, come here
You're bad
So, I win?
That doesn't count
You didn't steal it, he did!
I will give you another chance.
I've been wanting to hit you all along
Now if you managed to hit my face
I lose
Come on
Fighting your dad is my job
He always loses to me
She didn't get to touch my face
That doesn't count
Let's race cars
There is an 8 curve somewhere ahead
After this 8 curve, there is a sharp curve
After the sharp curve, at around 200 meters,
there is a road sign
Whoever passes the road sign first
is the winner
You have already lost 2 rounds.
I hope this time you will win
I need a good working partner
Let's do this
As long as you win this round
I will consider helping you
Doctor, how is Sampan Hung's condition?
Not optimistic. I'm afraid you can't all go in
You wait here
You are...
I'm Sir Sampan's colleague
My name is Bing Bing.
I'm from the Weapons Unit
Bing Bing?
I hope your last name is not Lee
My last name is Fan
Hello, I'm doing something important here
Let's talk later
Miss Fan Bing Bing
Now...
No
Mr Fan
How is his condition now?
Sir Sampan...
I'm sorry
I ruined your car
The car is minor. Your well-being
is more important
I am a failed agent
I'm not as competent as you
I am ashamed of myself
What can I do for you?
I wished...
You could save the earth
The Seed of God
Get it back
This is my final wish
Sir Sampan...
I will think about it
You shouldn't have to think
If you don't promise me
I will...
turn in my grave
Sir Sampan
I said I would think about it
I will try my best
I will do it
Sir Sampan
My condolences
Louis, how is he?
Gone
I have to make a call to help
with his funeral arrangements
My phone is still in the room
You were over-acting, did you know that?
It's not easy to play sissy!
Is it really that bad?
Nothing. I came back for my cell phone
You guys go ahead
Don't come near me
If you come near, I will squash
you with my finger
Squash you
I will squash you
This is our special agents' training centre
What kind of kung fu is that?
They are just fooling around
Is this also just fooling around?
No. They screwed up
Bing Bing
Sir Sampan
Did you say you have some new invention for me?
Just in time. I have just invented
a new cell phone
If it comes to cell phones,
the latest should be
from our company - uPhone 8s
Plus
You can have one each
I don't want your phone
This is from our Weapons' Unit
We spent 3 years working on it
It has 207 special functions
It's called Phon-omenal Phone!
Our uPhone 8s Plus
Has 707 special functions
707 eh? Does it shoot fire?
You made it!
Impressive, eh?
With a pirate charger,
not only will it shoot fire,
it will blow up too
This is a very dangerous weapon
When in danger, it can even
shoot out shock needles
You mean this?
Sir Sampan. What are you doing?
Making a call
I forgot to tell you
Our Phonomenal Phone...
has 207 special functions,
but one function is missing...
the call function
So it's a phone that cannot make calls
How can you miss that?
It's truly phenomenal!
Sir Sampan, don't hit me
How could you miss that?
Don't...
Sir Sampan, we found Iron Hawk
Macau Customs has verified
that Iron Hawk has arrived
Iron Hawk is Sir Condor's right-hand guy
He is usually active around
Cambodia and Thailand
His mission this time,
must have something to do with their business
with the Crescent in Macau
How did you get your hands on
such inside information?
We have an undercover working for them
But I don't know who he is
So let's go to Macau
Ask Tina to make arrangements for us
1 million dollars
The banker has won 2 times in a row
You should bet on the banker
Minors should not be playing cards
Let me do it
Kiddo, be careful not to lose
your underpants on the betting table
Face card...
It's a 9 or 10
You're dead
9 or 10...
Face card...
I can play with my eyes shut,
and still win over you
TV set...
Cute, eh?
That's impossible
I have corners
There...
Banker scores 0, Player scores 1
Player wins
Hey, don't go
- Don't mess around
- I can lend you some chips
You had better go now
I will donate your winnings to charity
This kid is rebellious. Let me deal with her
Go get changed for dinner
Okay
You...
What are you doing?
No...
You dared provoke me?
I will show you...
Amon
Louis
Ka-yan maybe in danger
Go check on her
Yes
Wait here
You should work on your punches? Try mine
Can you not see?
Wanna play bullfighting?
Come on...
Ouch...
Why are you taking pictures?
Why not?
Jedi
Ouch...
You used sleeping gas?
Well, you started it
Who are you?
Your father
Then I'm your mother
You think that's funny?
Louis. Is Ka-yan okay?
Where are my spare glasses?
What's going on?
Let go of her!
You alright?
If I call her
I wonder if she will take it
Sir Sampan, Louis has gone missing
Don't panic, I will find him
Anybody?
Anybody still alive?
I'm alive
Nobody has visited this place for a week
It's under renovation
Nobody will come to save you
Why don't you chase me
Little Chump!
Louis Luo
Why did you stick your nose into our business?
There are quite some people working with him
I will kill you right now
Wait a minute
This is from South America
A venomous bug found at the banks of the Amazon
with super reproductive power
These parasites love living in the body
of their host animal
They will lay eggs in a few hours
The eggs will turn into bugs
And suck up all the nutrients of the host
Then bite their way out of the host's body
And look for the next host
This is the law of nature
They look like chilly crayfish
Phoenix, Ape...
yank his mouth open
This bug is afraid of coldness
It will crawl to the warmest places
There are spikes on its legs
You can't spit them out
Wait till you die, and your body gets cold
Then it will bite through your body to get out
You women are so vicious
Okay, I should go now
Hey
Sir Condor is waiting for you
at the usual place
Well then, let's all leave
The sight of blood always gives me the chills.
I might pass out
I need to get my body warmer
You need to cool down
and let your body temperature drop
What are you doing?
Why did you save me?
Who are you?
Come back here
Phoenix!
Why did you save me?
Who are you?
Phoenix!
There he is
You Okay?
- Louis
- I'm okay
Let me do it
Good thing the tracker was activated
I almost got eaten up by his bug
Fortunately the girl with silvery hair
in the Crescent gang
The one that's called Phoenix, she saved me
She's also using this Phonomenal Phone
She can't be your people, can she?
It's possible
Milan!
This information is passed to me
by the Italian secret service
I can't read Italian
Who can read Italian?
Thanks
Speak Cantonese!
They said Crescent has a secret lab in Milan
Its security system is guaranteed No. 1
in the whole of Europe
It's full of dangerous traps
The stuff we are looking for
is definitely inside
They don't know about the Seed of God?
No, they don't
What we know is that
Condor has already left Eastern Europe
He will probably meet up
with Crescent these few days
Tell me about the security system of the lab
Tell me everything
- Yes
- I want every detail
This is the maximum security laboratory that
we have spent 18 months building
Without this card and my iris,
not even a fly can get in
Let me remind you
After this door is opened,
please hold your breath
and walk quietly
Any sound exceeding 25 decibels
along this hallway,
will trigger off the revolving laser blades
Intruders will be cut up like ground meat
Are you serious?
The laser blades run on the X and Y-axes.
It's vertically covered all around
Not even a mosquito can get away
Don't worry
The Seed of God is very safe in here
25 decibels
Revolving laser blades
That's good
Dr Peterson, shall we talk business now?
I thought we have already settled our business
We sell them and you get 30% of the money
We wish to sell them together
with the formula that only you know
That way the profit can be much higher
You can't do that
If that doesn't work, then we get 70%,
and you get 30%
Definitely not
Imagine we stop protecting you,
once you step out of this laboratory...
Condor and his men will get you
and torture you to death
How can you do business like this?
Who will want to work with people
like you anymore?
Do you think...
you have the chance to tell that to anyone?
What are you going to do?
This is the latest invention
In 72 hours,
it will make a copy of all your memories
How does it do that?
Sir Condor
According to my reliable sources
Snow has already killed Dr Peterson
However, they have duplicated all his memory
Along with the secret of the Seed of God
If we use the Seed of God
on the cultivation of cocaine
Our annual profit will grow at least ten-fold
- That's right
- I have already set up a meeting
for you two to meet Snow
at the San Siro Stadium
Impressive
I can't believe this little girl can actually
do better than a hacker
She's always been a hacker
Only that we can't tell from her face
That's right
If we want to get into the lab,
that means,
we have to duplicate the key to
the manager Sophia's house...
and also the image of her iris
Why do we need the image of her iris?
Because the image of the iris works
like a fingerprint
Everybody's iris image is unique
Sophia has been in Milan for 8 years,
but she hasn't had a boyfriend
in the past 7 years
She is extremely lonely
Then what is her taste in men like?
She likes men that wear trench coats
Her ex had been forced
to wear a trenchcoat day in day out
Sophia has been a super fan
of Alain Delon since childhood
That's why she is infatuated with men
that wears trench coats
Speaking of eccentricities
If...
we want to get...
the image of her iris,
we will need to find a man that
loves wearing trenchcoats
She is also in favour of men that...
are handsome,
has musical sense,
loving...
Where can we find such a perfect man?
Why are you cracking up?
He is totally referring to me
I have to conquer her
I...
love...
And so I got her eyeballs
If you like doing that, then you should go
Of course I should go
You don't think you are qualified
for that mission, do you?
Handsome, trenchcoat...
"New message"
"Our spy in the Crescent is called Phoenix"
"Contact her if you need to"
It's late
You didn't ask me to come here
just to have coffee with you, right?
What is it?
In the past 5 to 6 days
I keep wanting to ask you this question
Shoot
Phoenix, the girl with silvery hair,
is she an undercover from your side?
Undercover is a highly confidential topic.
How can I tell you?
If not,
why did she take such risk to save my life?
She sucked the bug out for me
Tell me, are you in love with her?
You tell me first. Is she your undercover?
Seriously?
I'm not telling you
You suck
Don't ask again
Even if you do, I won't tell you
Be serious,
do you know Phoenix?
You look smart and trendy,
but why are you so dumb when it comes to love?
I have always been dumb
You look like you know a lot about love
Let's change the subject
I don't want to change it
Tell me frankly
Do you have a girlfriend?
- No
- Then do you have a boyfriend?
Are you looking for some spanking?
Okay
I'll tell you
In fact, when it comes to love,
I am just as dumb
I had a wife
Divorced
Two years now. We've been divorced for 2 years
She said...
everyday she was afraid...
that I wouldn't come home after I left
Then, even if her husband had
any big accomplishments,
she couldn't tell anyone that...
her husband had saved the world
She can't even tell anyone what
her husband does for a job
If you change your job,
then may be she will come back to you
Being a secret agent for so long
I have made a lot of enemies
If I quit now, maybe I will die even sooner
I'm afraid...
she will suffer
I have a feeling you have a very good wife
Do you have a picture of her?
Not bad
Very pretty
She looks like a loving wife
You two look good together
This is the only one I have left
I'll bet you
That she will come back to you
Thanks
It's nice hanging out with you
I've been losing to you all along
Let's have another contest
See who reaches the hotel first
If you lose,
you buy me a 1982 red wine
If I lose, I buy you a 2012
Sounds like I'm having big advantage
You've smartened up
Phoenix is our undercover
The contest has started
You're bad
I can't imagine you can
go out of your way for love
So much that you would just let me win
You are a bad person
You are not much better than me
But I am really happy to be acquainted with you
We should celebrate
Let me order a bottle of champagne
Good. I haven't got trashed for a long time
That's fast
That can't be it
I haven't even made the call
- Hi
- Good evening. Room Service
That's quick
Yes. It's from the hotel
Good
Enjoy, Sir
Thank you
The service here is too impressive
Don't you dare hit me
That's another assassin from K-MAX
Who would have predicted...
that I would end up being injured like this
The day after tomorrow is
the Finals for AC Milan
All eyes will be on the match
This is the best time to make a move
But your condition is quite bad
Who can we send to seduce Sophia?
You're right about that
In fact, you look quite handsome too
Me...
Are you alright?
This is incredible
I dreamt about exactly the same scene
It's been more than a month
You were in my dreams
You have appeared in my dreams
for more than a month
OMG!
Why is this happening?
What did you see in your dreams?
I dreamt I was dying
I dreamt of you
I dreamt of this place
I dreamt of you and I together
The two of us...
We were doing...
I'm ashamed to say it
Say it please
I'm...
I'm too embarrassed to talk about it
Tell me
I'm...
Let's find a softer piece of ground to talk
Okay!
Let's go
I haven't touched a man in 7 years
You...
are a gift from heaven to me
No
I can't violate my goddess
I wished I was dead
Stay down for a while
In fact...
I've always wanted to do what
we did in my dreams
But...
it is hard to say it out loud
Do it...
Let me dim the lights
You're so romantic
Go now
Get down
Can you guess what I did to you in my dreams?
I don't know
In my dreams,
I kissed your feet
This is so original
Baby...
Do it...
Why is your eye blue?
I am wearing coloured Contact lens. Like it?
Yes. I like it
Vodka
Not spicy enough, have to add some chili sauce
Baby...
Use...
your mouth...
to feed...
me
Do it
I'm sorry
Are you alright?
I'm alright
Let me go clean up
- Clean up...
- You wait here
I wait here...
Come on
I can't relax with the lights on
Put them out
Run
I miss my wife
Okay. I'll call her
Sir Sampan, I'm all set
How's it going on your end?
I'm ready
Tell Louis,
there are 282 units of laser beams
in the security system,
with 0.25 meter's distance between them
There are 8 laser beam combinations
The last one to activate is based on
Descartes' rule of signs
So if they don't leave within 3 minutes
They are dead
But,
with your brother's skills,
that shouldn't be a problem
- Don't worry
- Sir Sampan, thank you
You're welcome
It's good to have family
5 billion
3 billion
No
No deal then
"Iron Hawk: I'm inside the lab"
"Sir Sampan: Get to the lab at once"
Where is he?
- Hello
- Has your brother arrived?
- Not yet
- We have to hurry. We are running out of time
Louis is here
How's it going?
Sir Sampan has familiarized himself
with the security system
Then we should move fast
Okay
Once the laser blades have been activated,
you must evacuate within 3 minutes
Or your live will be at risk
The range is about 52 meters
I weigh 70 kg
Louis, be careful
Let's do it
It's you again?
You shouldn't have to save him
He's a life after all
Mr Luo
You are a good man
Thank you
You're blinded again
The needles are poisonous
Since last time
I have learnt my lesson
and got lasik surgery done
I wore glasses to fool you
You cheater
Haven't I told you?
I'll find a way to neutralise the poison in you
I can still hang on for a while
We'd better get the Seed of God now
This is the doctor's memory drive
Let's go
What do you want?
What are you doing?
I am warming up my body
to suck out the bug inside you
I didn't eat any bug
That's right
Don't suck
You did it for me once
Louis, what are you doing?
What are you laughing about?
Never seen a handsome man?
Mom, I'm back in town
Then why don't you come home?
I have something important
to hand over to the police
I'll come home right after that
I made soup
Come back to drink it
It's ginseng with bird's nest,
banana and meat buns soup. It's good
Ka-yan and Amon will be home before me
Why don't you serve them first?
Mr KK wants to meet you now,
so he can praise you in person
You are a hero
You are a big hero
Try "super"
Super
I know
I think "big" can better express
The respect I have for him now
Right
Big
And handsome
More handsome than you and me
I don't know about that
If we go back 20 years,
I'm sure Sir Sampan was
a top-notch handsome man
You're too nice
Well, at least he had been handsome once
A supermarket coupon of $588
It's very practical
Thank you
If there's nothing else, I shall go now
Don't
Please sit...
I still have a lot of compliments for you
Sit
Boss
You have been speaking for 90 minutes already
That's about the length of a whole movie
Sit
Then I will continue to compliment on
our undercover heroine
Boss
I think...
you can write down all
your praises of me in a letter
That way, my mom can read it too
Then I will start with something
your mom shouldn't read about
At such a young age,
how is it possible that
you have such a great body?
Now praise me
Praise you
Just now he was making fun of your age
It's okay
I am old
Let go of me
What do you people want?
You are still so young,
you just have to work hard
Sooner or later you will get to higher places
I will. I will work hard
With a good boss like you,
I will bend backwards for the job
They took my mom
Why don't you go after him?
I'm off
As courtesy, I should also chase
after them, right?
Of course
Don't run
Tell him about the supermarket coupon
What is it?
They are not valid on public holidays
Good. You've got guts
You dare to come here
I got the stuff with me. I want to see my mom
You are in no position to make any deals
I can kill you both
And the stuff will naturally become mine
The thermal box that he is holding
has a special device
He only has to press a button,
the Seed of God will be burned instantly
along with the doctor's memory drive
So you'd rather destroy it than
letting anyone get his hands on it
I think I had better allow you to see your mom
Take her out here
Mom
Did you sleep well in here?
Did you eat well?
Oh, who would have guessed in
a crappy place like this,
there is actually a toilet
You untie my mom first,
then I will give you the Seed of God
This is my turf. I make the rules
Give me the seeds
Or would you like to witness how Iron Hawk...
break your mother's legs?
Get lost
I just need to press my watch
Sir Condor will instantly become a dead condor
Hurry up, let go of my mom
Sir Condor?
He is never Sir Condor
You are welcome to kill him
Me
Have always been me
He is the brother of Iron Hawk
- his name is Iron Tiger
He is my bodyguard
I purposely make people think he is Sir Condor
So who do you think I am?
His sweet little mistress?
What is this? Party time?
Let Iron Tiger go
Or I will put a bullet in your mom's underarm
Don't worry
She won't die, but there will be a lot of blood
and it will be painful
No
Give me the seeds
Let me see if they are the real stuff
Water
This is really good stuff
When you get back, put 5 billion Euro into
a designated account of mine
Then I will release your mom
How can you not keep your promise?
I'm a woman, not a gentleman
How can you expect me to keep a promise?
Stand by
I'm ready
Get out of here!
I want to speak with my mom
I can hear you
Yes, but we have to tie up your hands
Go ahead
What are you doing?
Son
That's enough
Mom
There is something I've been wanting
to tell you for a long time
Go ahead
In fact
I have already mastered the skill of...
Breaking Free
That is awesome
Get her out of here
Quickly
Let's go
Let's go get mom
We can still use this old hag. Lock her up
Get in quick
Hey
You're out-numbered. You can't beat the 3 of us
Don't wait for me, I can handle it
You're out-numbered. You can't beat the 2 of us
Be careful, Louis
This chick is not to be belittled
You think you two are good enough to beat me?
Don't forget I'm still here
Oh, I have forgotten there is another one
You're out-numbered...
You can't beat the 3 of us together
Golden shield and iron clothes?
She is a tip top kung fu master
Old lady, I'm growing to like you more and more
Iron clothes?
Try my kicks
Why?
She is so afraid for her breasts
They could be fake?
Keep attacking
They're real
Phoenix, feed her the bug
Mangoes
All this fighting...
for the sake of some mangoes
Mom, put this on
Put this on
Quick
Mom
Leave now
- My hat
- You go first
"Parachute"
Louis
Grab this
You go first
There's no time
Go
Hello
Hello?
Who is this?
It's Sampan. That's right
- What's up?
- Nothing
It's my day off. Thought I should
give you a call
Where are you?
I'm on a plane
Any problems?
No
Okay, I have to go
The plane is about to taking off
Okay then
Bye
Hey...
Hello
About your job,
I do understand
But if there are any dangerous missions,
try to get out of it
You have to stay alive...
so as to save the world
Stop nagging
I have to go
I will call you again when I have the chance
Bye
"Ejection Button"
I called my wife!
- Happy birthday
- Thank you
Thank you
It's you
This is awesome
Mom
This is Mr KK, he is Sir Sampan's boss
Your Dad's boss?
Mrs Luo, you are very pretty
Thank you for saving the world
Don't mention it
I have to thank you on behalf
of the whole world
You have such a great son
I must pay you a long compliment
I'm happy with your performance this time
You can take me to a movie tonight
Too late
I belong to someone already
Who is that?
Baby
I think she is more suitable for me
How old are you?
28?
You don't look it at all
You are looking too good for a 28 year old
Sir Sampan
Do you drink soup every day?
Why is his picture here?
This used to be the picture of my dad
It's still the picture of your dad
Looks like I'll have another dad soon
Sir Sampan
Are you alright?
I am okay
How are you feeling?
Take me outside
Okay
Louis, who are you waiting for
Phoenix said she'd come
Look, she's here
Sorry I'm late
Happy Birthday
Thank you
You guys chat
How do you do? I'm Louis Luo
Ignore him
He is a con man that I just caught
Thought I should just come here with him
instead of dropping him off
at the police station
I thought...
he was your boyfriend
You think I have such bad taste?
Hey, that's a personal attack
You think good looking guys can”: be cons?
Beware of good looking guys
Shall we have dinner tonight?
I just got my new mission. I'm going to Brazil
I'll see you when I get back
Okay
Bye
Hey
Have my plane ready,
I'm flying to Brazil tonight
Why is Sir Sampan's picture hanging here?
Are you jealous?
I can put yours on the wall tomorrow, okay?
Oh, that's not necessary
Just change this one to black-and-white
Happy Birthday to you...
Now the Luos and myself
are the only people that...
knows about the existence of the Seed of God
We haven't made the world a better place
But then at least we haven't made it worse
Sampan Hung
Why don't you turn around?
No
I am afraid I would lose you when I turn around
I heard you have really saved the world
And you made time to call me before
you thought you were dying
You're getting taller
Stop it
Let's take a selfie
This way...
Take one holding each other
Okay. Let me hold you
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org